Guide to the Robert Fitch Papers WAG.261
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI. 2015 Accretion
  - New Corruption BK (Research Files/ Articles by Others) (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Resarch Files/Articles by Others (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Petras (Research Files/Articles by Others) (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - How We Are (Research Files/Articles by Others) (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Francepa (Research Files/Articles by Others) (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Organizing (Research Files/Articles by Others) (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Sellout 2 (Research Files/Articles by Others) (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Swedish Language (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Red Family (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Berkeley (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Shame City Revisited (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Socialism (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Jewish Book (Part 1) [1848 - H] (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Jewish Book Part II [I-X] (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Journ Part II [M-W] (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Arendt Chapter (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - New Projects (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Labor Proposals (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Union Democracy (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - United Auto (UAW) (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Trip (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Think Tank (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Taking Chapter (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Nietzsche (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - New Union Bk (Part I) [A-I] (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - New Union Bk (Part II) [H-W] (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Left Economics (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - MR Econ (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Left Labor (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - LIU (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Left (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Left AZ (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Intro: Revolt Against Solidarity (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - TDU Chapter (Box 21, Folder 41-42)
  - Teamsters (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Revolt Against Solidarity (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - UFW Chapter (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - SOS Chapters (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Unite Chapter Part 1 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Teachers (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Local 196 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Unite Chapter (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Sell Out! (Part 2) (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
  - Sell Out (Part 3) (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Sell Out! (Part 1) [A-F] (Box 22, Folder 4-5)
  - Corruption Book (Part 1) [A-H] (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Corruption Book (Part II) [M-W] (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Card Check Part II [comments - Mark] (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Card Check Part III (Moberg-Z) (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Intro Chapter (Part III) [I-W] (Box 22, Folder 10-11)
  - Intro Chapter (Part III) [D-H] (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Intro Chapter (Part I) ['85-C] (Box 22, Folder 13-14)
  - History MOB (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Hidden Cost (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Unite Chapter Part II (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Carpenters (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Microsoft User Data (Part II) (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Bibliography SOS (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Organizing (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Union Democracy (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Willie and George (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Politics Course (Part II) [Power.f] (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Politics Course (Part II) [RonCarey.final-W] (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Politics Chapter (Part I) [B-Ron Carey. final] (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Pension Chapters (Part I) [2004-N] (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Pension Chapters (Part II) [P-W] (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Central States Chapter (Part II) (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Microsoft User Data Part I (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Los Angeles Labor (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Liuna Chapter (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Laborers Reform (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Union Book (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Solidarity Chapter (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Journ Part I (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - ILA (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Microsoft Data Part VIII (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Microsoft Data Part VI (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Microsoft User Data (Part V) [Word Work File] (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Microsoft User Data (Part IV) [Word Work File] (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Microsoft User Data Part III [Word Work File] (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Central States Chapter Part I [H-S] (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Conclusion, CH (Part 1) [A-L] (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - ATU Part I (Bus - H) (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - ATU Part II [I-W] (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Conclusion Chapter (Part III) [SEIU. text -W] (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Conclusion Chapter (Part II) [M-SEIU.NUT] (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Files as of 4/10/2007 (Box 23, Item 1)
  - Files as of 9/21/2008 (Box 23, Item 2)
  - Files As of 3/1/2009 (Box 23, Item 3)
  - Files As of 5/20/2008 (2) (Box 23, Item 4)
  - Files as of 5/20/2008 (1) (Box 23, Item 5)
  - Files as of 2/4/2010 (1) (Box 23, Item 6)
  - Files as of 2/4/2010 (2) (Box 23, Item 7)
  - Files as of 3/7/2010 (Box 23, Item 8)
  - Unlabled CD 2 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Fitch LM-2 Floppy Disk (Box 23, Item 10)
  - Files 22 III 09 (Box 23, Item 11)
  - Unlabled CD 1 (Box 23, Item 12)
- Series VII. 2016 Accretion
  Scope and Contents
  The bulk of this accretion consists of materials created or collected by Fitch's friends and colleagues in an effort to commemorate his life and work. Materials include correspondence and pamphlets from Fitch's memorial service, with most of the correspondence consisting of emails sent between Jane LaTour and Fitch's former coworkers, family, and friends. Also included are materials regarding the first five annual Robert Fitch memorial lectures held at LaGuardia Community College from 2012 and 2016. The accretion also includes articles about the release of Fitch's book The Assassination of New York as an e-book in 2014, as well as a transcript of a lecture he gave at the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Archives in 1999.
  - E-Book "Assassination", 2014 (Box 24)
  - "Assassination" E-Book, 2013-2014 (Box 24)
  - Speeches - Brecht Forum (BF), 1999-2011 (Box 24)
  - Tributes, 2006-2011 (Box 24)
  - Left Forum, 2006-2011 (Box 24)
  - Fitch May Memorial, 2011 (Box 24)
  - Untitled (Robert Fitch Memorial / Brecht Forum), 2011 (Box 24)
  - Contact Info for Brecht Forum (BF), 2011-2013 (Box 24)
  - Researchers Interested in Bob Fitch Collection, 2011-2016 (Box 24)
  - LaGuardia Community College Personnel File for Robert Fitch, 1996-2010 (Box 24)
  - 5th Annual Bob Fitch Lecture, 2016 (Box 25)
  - 3rd Annual Bob Fitch Lecture at LaGuardia, 2014 (Box 25)
  - 2nd Annual Bob Fitch Lecture (LaGuardia), 2013-2015 (Box 25)
  - Bob Fitch 1st Annual Memorial Lecture, 2012 (Box 25)
  - Industrial Worker - Assassination of New York, 2014 (Box 25)